

# Hana Le

# Entry Level Data Analyst | Statistician

### **My Contact**

Marsfield, NSW 2122





in linkedin.com/in/hanglth



mana-le.com



🦈 github.com/Hana-Le



PR in progress

# **Education Background**

- Macquarie University Masters of Applied Statistics Completed in Dec 2022 **WAM 85**
- University of Queensland Master of Project Management
- Vietnam National University, Hanoi Bachelor of Science

### **Technical Skills**

- R
- SQL
- Tableau
- **Excel Data Analysis**
- Python
- Data Visualisation
- Statistical Modeling
- Data Analysis

### **Soft Skills**

- Skilled in stakeholder partnership management across sectors
- Adaptable to diverse working styles
- Experienced in diverse team collaboration
- Solution-focused and data-driven

#### **About Me**

A recent Applied Statistics graduate with a WAM of 85 and a passion for utilizing computational techniques to analyze and interpret data. Proficient in R, SQL, Tableau, and Excel with in-depth knowledge of contemporary statistical methods. Seeking opportunities to further develop skills and bring 6+ years of project management experience in UN and NGO settings, including data collection and analysis, to the table.

## **Professional Experience**

#### Data Entry Officer | Avant Mutual

Key responsibilities:

Reviewing, verifying and compiling data in the database system.

#### **Program Officer | Oxfam Organisation**

2018 - 2019

Key responsibilities:

Design and implementation management of a series of gender and development projects, delivered in partnership with both nongovernment organisations and government agencies.

#### Project Coordinator | International Labour Organization

2015 - 2017

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USD1.5m portfolio of projects aimed at improving labour practices in private sector enterprises in Viet Nam.

#### Project Manager | Care International Organisation

2010 - 2014

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USD1m portfolio of projects aimed at delivering public health interventions for disadvantaged and vulnerable communities.

### **Achievements**

- · Successfully managed all projects in charge, including delivering on time, within budget, and to the agreed quality specifications.
- · Achieved a full scholarship for the master's program at Queensland University.